제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
야! 내 몸 어디에다 내가
'핑크 플로이드'라고 별명 붙였게?
Oh! Hey, you guys, guess what part
of my body I nicknamed Pink Floyd?
말 하지마!
Shut up.
재키는 귀엽다고 그랬었는데
Well, Jackie thought it was cute.
재키는 이제 여기 없잖아
Well, Jackie's not here anymore.
오늘 아침에 재키네 집에 갔었는데
I was over at Jackie's this morning.
축 처져 있더라
너무 우울해 하더라구
She's so down.
It's really depressing.
이별의 고통이 아주 크구만, 응?
She's taking the breakup
pretty hard, huh?
앗싸!
Cool!
시끄러, 너는 애기처럼 울어댔잖아
Shut up, man. You cried like a baby.
Whoa. I did not cry.
I had something in my eye.
나 안 울었어
눈에 뭐가 들어갔었단 말야
일주일 내내?
For a week?
알러지가 있단 말야, 알아?
I have allergies, alright?
우는 게 뭐가 나빠?!
Is it so wrong to feel?!
하여간, 재키는 꼴이 말이 아냐
Anyway, Jackie's like,
in really bad shape.
켈소, 인제 너랑 재키는
아무 상관도 없는 사이잖아
So, Kelso, now that you and
Jackie are no longer an item,
그러니까 내가 재키한테
데이트신청해도 되겠지?
um, I can ask her out, right?
뭐? 안돼
너 언제부터 재키 좋아했는데?
What? No. Since when do you like Jackie?
그래 페즈, 좋은 생각이 아닌 거 같다
Yeah Fez, I don't think that's a good idea.
그래, 페즈, 그러지 마
재키는 실연을 극복하는 중이야
Yeah, Fez man, that's a bad idea.
Jackie's on the rebound right now.
- 좀 쉬게 해 줘
- 뭐?
Why don't you just give her a break.
What?
넌 또 언제부터 재키 좋아했는데?
Since when do you like Jackie?
뭐야, 여기 있는 놈들 전부
이제 재키가 좋아진 거야?
Alright, does everybody
here now like Jackie?
난 아직 아냐
I still don't.
고마워, 에릭
Thank you, Eric.
페즈, 하이드 말은 재키가 지금
너무 약해져 있다는 거야
Fez, Hyde's just saying that
Jackie's really vulnerable right now.
그래, 그러니까 다시 쎄지기 전에
잽싸게 작업 들어가야 된단 말야
Yes. So I must move fast before
she gets her self-esteem back.
하긴 걔가 그렇게 축 처져 있을
만도 하지. 나한테 차였잖아
Yeah, you can't blame her for being
down. After all, I did dump her.
니가 차인 거겠지!
Actually, she dumped you.
야, 나 꼬치꼬치 따지는 거 싫어하거든?
Hey, I don't like to get into specifics.
그럼, 산에 가서 혼자 떠들던가
Oh, go tell it on the mountain.
아무도 내가 재키한테
데이트 신청하는 건 못 막아
Nothing will stop me from
asking Jackie on a date.
닌자라 해도..
Not even ninjas...
비켜라! 재키를 내놔
아무도 날 못 막는다
Stand back! I want Jackie,
and no one will stop me.
재키는 어림없다
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
You cannot have Jackie.
내 이 빠른 몸놀림으로
널 꼼짝못하게 해 주마
I will disable you with my cat-like swiftness.
오, 그래?
Oh, yeah?
그래
Yeah.
오, 그래? / 그래
Oh, yeah? / Yeah.
Oh.
페즈
Fez. Go ahead, Fez.
하고 싶은대로 해
그래봤자, 넌 외국인이라 안돼
그래도 시도나 해 보던가
Ask Jackie out, she won't go 'cause
you're foreign, but go ahead and ask.
그래 할거야
You're damn right I will.
아뵤~!
Hiyaaaa!
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
리사 로빈 켈리 (로리 포먼)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 오흥민(echem@nate)
제작지원 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 오흥민(echem@nate)
제작지원 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
2x22 Jackie Moves on
Apr 03, 2000 on FOX
안돼, 새 헤어 롤러 사라고
15달러나 줄 순 없어
No Laurie, I am not giving you
fifteen dollars for new hot rollers.
생머리로 다녀도 세상 안 끝나
Straight hair is not the end of the world.
사실 누나의 세상은 평범한 사람들보다
훨씬 쪼꼬맣고 천박하잖아요
Actually, Mom, Laurie's
world is a lot smaller,
much more shallow
than the average persons'.
제발요, 엄마. 웨이브 머리는
제 자존심이란 말이에요
Come on, Mom. Curls are
important for my self-esteem.
네 자존심을 위해서
또 뭘 해야 되는지 알아?
Oh, you know what else might
be good for your self-esteem?
동네 창녀짓 그만 하기!
Not being the village whore.
함 해보자는 거냐, 꼬맹아?
Are you trying to start
something with me, little boy?
너 일하는 동안 난 할일없이 앉아서
너 씹을 궁리만 하면 되는데도?
Because while you have to go to work,
all I have to do is sit around
and think up ways to hurt you.
글쎄, 동네 창녀짓하느라
그럴 시간이나 있을까 몰라
Oh, I don't know. As village whore,
I would think your day's all full up.
닥쳐 / 이겼다!
Shut up. / Ha! I win!
둘다 그만두지 못해!
You're both wrong, so can it!
넌 죽었어
You're dead.
아이고, 무서워라
Oooh, I'm so scared.
여보
Kitty,
시내에 작은 프랑스 레스토랑있잖아?
you remember that little
French restaurant downtown?
프랑스 레스토랑요?
Frenchies?
그거 하나밖에 없잖아
The one and only.
내가 오늘밤에 두자리 예약해뒀어
I made reservations for tonight.
Forman, party of two.
당신이 이런 걸 다 알아서 하다니, 여보
Well now, this is so
spontaneous of you, Red.
내 '코스모'잡지에서 보고
이러는 건 아니겠죠?
You haven't been reading my
“Cosmo,” have you?
여보, 우리 쫙 빼입고 가자고
당신 우리 어머니 목걸이도 하고
Come on, Kitty. We'll get all dressed up,
you can even wear my mother's necklace.
아!
Oh... The necklace. Yay!
그 목걸이!
신난다!
서둘러라, 에릭. 늦겠다
Come on, Eric, we're gonna be late.
- 다녀올께요, 엄마
- 다녀오렴, 얘야
Bye, Mom. / Bye, honey.
큰일났네
Oh, this is awful.
왜요, 엄마
프랑스 요리도 괜찮아요
Come on, Mom.
French food's not that bad.
'폼 프리'나 주문하세요
그게 감자튀김이에요, 알았죠?
Just order pommes frites--
they're french fries, you know.
그게 아냐, 그 목걸이
그게 없거든
No, honey, the necklace.
I don't have it anymore.
정말요? 어쩌셨는데요?
Really. What'd you do with it?
아니다
Nothing. I said nothing.
아무 것도 아냐
엄마, 도박으로 그 목걸이 날리셨어요?
Mom, did you gamble the necklace away?
그만해
작업하러 가게 해줄테니까
Okay, stop it Laurie.
I'll make you get a job.
갔다올께요!
Bye!
좋아, 페즈, 재키한테 데이트
신청하는 건 엄청난 기회야
Okay, Fez. Asking Jackie out
is a big opportunity for you.
And if she says no, don't cry.
걔가 싫다고 해도?
울면 안돼
그냥 재치있고 정중하게
Just be witty and polite.
대본대로만 하자
Stick to the script.
가장 중요한 건?
Most importantly, is speak
slowly and enunciate.
발음을 천천히
정확하게 하는 거야
여보세요?
Hello?
여보세요, 재키?
잘 있었니?
Hello, Jackie?
How are you doing today?
나도 잘 있었어
요새 날씨 참 좋지?
I am fine. Nice weather lately, huh?
오늘밤에 나랑 저녁식사같이
하지 않을래?
Would you like to go have
dinner with me tonight?
좋아
Okay.
잠깐, 근데 너 누구니?
Oh wait, who is this?
나야, 페즈
It's me, Fez.
에이
Oh. Okay.
그러지 뭐
난 그냥 너랑 켈소가
이제 안 만나니까..
I just thought that since you
and Kelso are no longer dating --
마이클은 어때?
How is Michael doing?
어, 괜찮은 가봐
Uh, fine I guess.
Actually, he seems dumber.
사실은 더 멍청해졌어
그거 잘 됐네
나도 잘 지내거든
Well, you know what? That's
great, 'cause I'm doing fine, too.
딱 좋아 (fine)
Just fine.
니가 세련된(fine) 여자라면
난 멋진(dandy) 남자지
Well, if you are fine, then I am dandy.
너랑 나, 멋지고 세련됐지 (fine and dandy)
(비꼬는 말투로 '좋네, 됐어'란 의미도 있음)
You and me, fine and dandy.
끊었냐?
Did you hang up?
아니 / 8시에 데리러 갈까?
No. / Pick you up at eight?
좋아(Fine) / 멋져(Dandy)
Fine. / Dandy.
준비 다 했어요, 가요
Okay, I'm all ready, so let's go.
우와, 당신 멋진데
Wow, you look great.
당신도 아주 멋있어요, 가요
And you look sharp yourself, so, let's go.
당신 그 목걸이 안 한거야?
Hey, weren't you gonna wear
my mother's necklace?
여기 있어요!
Here it is!
멋지죠? 잃어버리까봐 안에다 했어요
그러니까 출발하자구요
Doesn't it look nice? I tuck it in so
I won't lose it, so let's hit the road.
그런데, 어머니가 당신한테
준 그 목걸이같지 않은데?
Well you know that, didn't really look
like the one that she gave you.
맞다니까요. 똑같아 보이죠?
이게 그거니까요
Oh sure it does. It looks just
like it! Because it is it!
이제 늙어서 자기 어머니가 나한테
준 목걸이도 못 알아보는군요
Now look who's getting old, doesn't even
remember what necklace his mother gave me.
자, 얼른 가자구요
So, let's move it out.
너, 핫도그 정말 좋아하는구나
Boy Laurie, you really liked that hot dog.
씹지도 않고 삼키냐!
You didn't even chew it.
야 하이드, 아버지 날도 다가오는데
Oh, hey Hyde, Father's Day is coming up.
"정말 우리 아빠세요?"
말하는 연습 안해도 되겠니?
Shouldn't you practice saying,
“Hi, are you my daddy?”
그런데 로리, 공중위생국장이
전화했더라
Oh, by the way Laurie,
the surgeon general called.
너 때문에 성병약이 바닥나 버렸다고
그만 좀 사 먹으래
He wanted you to stop
hoarding all the penicillin.
너 감옥 가서도 밥상머리에서
그렇게 재수없게 굴면
You know, when you're in
prison your bad table manners
그거 보구 떡대 아저씨들
흥분해서 껄떡댈껄
will probably just be a turn-on
for some guy named Tank.
그래? 거기로 네 남편 면회 오거든
Well, maybe when you're
there for a conjugal visit
나한테 살살 하라고
말 좀 해 주라
you can ask him to take it easy on me.
그래? 그러면...
Oh yeah? Well...
니 팔둑 굵다, 그래
Nice hair.
뭐야, 벌써 밑천 다 떨어진 거야?
Oh, Laurie. Are you all outta putdowns?
그래, 나 오늘 상태 안 좋은가봐
에릭한테도 당했다니까
Yeah, I guess I'm having an
off day. Even Eric burned me.
에릭한테도 당했어?
너 완전히 맛이 갔구나?
Eric burned you?
You are totally lame.
그러게, 열라 비참하지 않냐?
에릭한테 까지
I know, isn't that pathetic? Eric.
내가 뭐?
What about me?
귀신도 제말하면 온다더니
Speaking of the spindly-armed devil.
뭐가 그렇게 비참해?
What's so pathetic?
아냐, 넌 알거 없어, 쪼다야
Nothing. At least, nothing we
can share with you, Gomer.
그래? 그러면..
Oh yeah? Well...
니 팔뚝 굵다, 그래
Nice hair.
뭐?
What?
재키, 무지 비싼 밥 맛있어?
So, Jackie. How is your
very expensive dinner?
훌륭해. 그래도 마이클의 빈자리를
음식으로 채우고 있는 건 아냐
It's great. And I'm not
replacing Michael with food.
그거 다 먹은 거니?
Are you gonna finish that?
그래, 괜찮아
Oh, that's okay.
알다시피, 이 식당은 무지 비싼 걸로
아주 유명하거든
You know, this restaurant is very well
known for their very expensive dinners.
- 그렇지만 널 위해서라면...
- 버터 좀 집어줘
- But for you it's--
- Pass the butter.
아, 버터
Ah, the butter.
그러고 보니
재밌는 얘기가 생각나는데
That reminds me of an amusing anecdote.
요전날 지하실에 있는데..
Well the other day,
I was in the basement-
마이클도 거기 있었니?
Was Michael there?
- 응, 그런데 말야...
- 걘 정말 바보야
- Yes. Anyway--
- He is such a jerk.
그래, 그러니까
그 재밌는 얘기가 말야
Yes, so anyway, back to
my amusing anecdote.
요전날, 내가 신발끈을
묶고 있는데...
Well the other day, I was
tying my shoe-- / Ask first!
다 안먹었어요!
페즈, 오늘밤에 너랑
여기 오게 돼서 너무 좋다
Fez, I am so glad I came
out with you tonight.
정말?
Really?
그래, 굶어죽을 뻔 했어
Mmm. I was starving!
그래서, 어떻게 됐어?
So, what happened?
재키한테 키스했냐?
Did you kiss her?
했으면 넌 죽었어
'Cause I'll kill you if you kissed her.
아니, 키스는 무슨 키스
Oh, no. I didn't want to kiss her,
휴지나 주고 싶더라
I wanted to give her a napkin.
내내 얼굴에 음식으로
칠을 하고 했었단 말야
There was not a moment when
she did not have a faceful of food.
정말 토할 뻔했다니까
I was disgusted.
정말? 전부 다 용서해 주지, 친구!
Really? Hey, all is forgiven, buddy!
좋아, 하이드
Okay, fine Hyde.
너 로리가 나에 대해서 한 말 가르쳐
주기 싫은가 본데, 난 신경안써
You don't want to tell me what Laurie
said about me, I'm fine with that.
말해잖아, 아무말도 안했어
Telling you man,
she didn't say anything.
그렇겠지, 로리가 또 좀 유명하냐?
Uh-huh, right, because I mean
that's what Laurie's known for --
'암말도 안하는 싸가지' 로 말이지
not saying bitchy things.
야 하이드, 진짜로는
뭐라고 그랬는데?
Hey, Hyde, what did
Laurie say about Eric?
나중에 말해 줄께, 장난 아냐
I'll tell you later, man. It's so bad.
웃기거든? 근데 장난 아냐
Funny, but bad.
아무 것도 아니라며
You got nothing.
뭐? 그래 맞아, 아무것도 아냐
Huh? Yeah, yeah, I got nothing.
됐어, 난 신경안써
Okay, fine, I don't care.
여름캠프 얘기구나, 그렇지?
She told you about summer camp, right?
얘들이 나 "오줌싸개"라고
놀렸었다. 그래 됐냐?
Fine, they called me Doctor Pee Pee.
침대 윗층에서 자는 게 무서웠어
그때 난 10살이었단 말야
I couldn't sleep on the
top bunk and I was ten. So..
그래서, 누가 신경이나 쓴대?
난 오줌싸개야, 난..
you know, who cares?
I'm Doctor Pee Pee. I'm...
오-줌 싸-개
Doc-tor Pee-Pee.
오줌싸개?!
Doctor Pee Pee?!
너한테 정말 딱이네!
You are so Doctor Pee Pee.
아, 정말?
Oh, really... Big Chief Brown Bottom?
똥싸개야?
미안하다 친구, 정말 미안해
다들 입 다물어
I'm sorry man, I'm sorry.
Just everyone shut up.
저녁은 어떠셨어요?
Hey, how was dinner?
좋았단다. 네 아빠가 그놈의 목걸이
타령 지겹게 한 거 빼고는
Fine. Except your father wouldn't
shut up about that stupid necklace.
여보, 뭐가 있는게 분명한데
왜 말을 안 해주는 거야?
Look Kitty, obviously
something's going on here,
so why don't you
just tell me what it is.
잃어버렸어?
Did you lose it?
아뇨
No.
누구 빌려줬어?
Did you lend it to somebody?
아뇨
No.
그럼 도대체 어떻게 된거야?
Then what the hell happened?
저당잡혔어요, 됐어요?
전당포에다 맡겼다구요
I hocked it, okay? I hocked it,
I pawned it, I hocked it.
돌아가신 우리 어머니 목걸이를
전당포에 맡겼다고?
You pawned my dead mother's necklace?
그래요. 그리고 하나도 안 미안해요
그 돈으로 먹을 거 샀어요
Yes. And I'm not sorry
'cause we got groceries for it,
그러니까 안 미안해요, 안 미안해
하나도 안 속상하다구요
so I'm not sorry, I'm not sorry,
and I don't feel bad!
오, 에릭, 많이 속상하구나
Oh, Eric, I feel so bad.
속상하시다구요? 로리가 온동네에
오줌싸개 얘기를 했단 말이에요
Mom, you feel bad? Laurie told
everyone about Doctor Pee Pee.
오 얘야, 그건 속상한게 아니지
Oh honey, that's not so bad, that's cute.
그건 귀엽잖아
- 나도 그 얘기는 많은 사람들한테..
- 엄마!
Oh please, I have told that
story to so many-- / Mom!
난 아무한테도 그 얘기 한 적 없다
I didn't tell that story to anybody.
마이클 사진들을 특수 마이클 상자에
전부 다 넣고 나니까
So then, after I finished putting all my
pictures of Michael in my special Michael box,
걔를 완전히 잊게 되더라니까
I realized that I'm so totally over him.
거짓말. 니 꼴을 좀 봐!
You liar. Look at yourself!
계속 그렇게 아구 터지게
먹어대면 너 금방....
And if you keep stuffing your
face like this, you're gonna get--
그말만 했단 봐
너 죽어!
Don't you dare say it, you bitch..
...뚱땡이될껄
...Fat.
안돼, 안돼에에에!
No. Noooo!!
파이 5개를 다 먹어가는데도
마이클 생각은 전혀 안 나
Yup. I've almost finished my fifth pie
and I'm still completely over Michael.
아냐
No.
그만해
Stop.
잠깐
Wait.
음~ 블루베리!
Mmm. Blueberry!
느낌이 좀 이상해
Huh. I'm feeling kind of weird.
안돼, 이게 뭐야?
Oh no, what's happening to me?
세상에, 어떡해, 어쩜 좋아
Oh my God, oh goodness,
oh gracious, oh my!
파이 그만 먹어
No more pie for you.
좋아, 가자 뚱땡아
Okay, let's go fatty.
좀 집어 넣어봐, 재키
Suck it in, Jackie.
세상에, 도나, 너무 무서워
어떻게든 해야겠다
Oh my God Donna, I'm scared.
I have to control myself.
그래? 그럼 우선 그 육포 먼저
이리 주고 시작하자
Okay. Well, then, let's start by
you handing Donna the jerky.
손 치워, 이 날강도야
Back off, you Amazon.
난 시간이 조금 필요한 것 뿐이야
Look, I just need more time.
좀전에 내가 육포집을 때 손을
치는 짓은 뚱땡이나 하는 짓이야
Okay, you slapping my hand
when I tried to take your jerky
is something a fat girl would do.
로리, 네가 하이드한테
뭐라고 했는지 알아
Okay, Laurie. I know what you told Hyde.
뭔 소리하는 거야, 멍청아?
What are you talking about, loser?
그 캠프 얘기 맞지?
오줌싸개 얘기 말야. 넌 죽었어
The camp story? Doctor
Pee Pee? You're dead.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 쉿. TV 본다고 생각해 / 알았어
- What's going on?
- Shh. Pretend it's TV. / Okay.
나도 네 비리에 대해서 좀 알지
Well, I know some pretty horrible
things about you, too, little lady.
얘들아
Fellas,
로리는 콧털, 다리털, 눈썹, 발가락털
날개쭉지털까지 밀고 다닌댄다
Laurie here waxes her lips, legs,
eyebrows, toes, and shoulder blades.
5학년 때, 에릭이 육체미 도장을
다녔었는데, 왜 그랬을까?
In the fifth grade, Eric sent
away for the Charles Atlas kit.
여자애한테 개무시 당했기 때문이지
'Cause a girl kicked sand in his face.
- 너 고등학교 뒷문으로 들어갔잖아
- 넌 안 그랬어?
You stuffed in high school. / So did you.
작년에 지 생일용돈 다 털어서
'등 맛사지기'를 샀는데
Last year, Laurie used all her birthday
money to buy a "back massager."
그걸 사실은 어디다 사용하는지는
온 집안 식구가 다 알지
Which isn't fooling anyone, by the way.
그건 아무것도 아냐! 지난번에
내가 얘 방에 들어갔는데
Well, that's not as bad as when
I walked in on you in bed
침대에서 도로시 해밀 포스터 갖고는...
70년대 여자 피겨 스케이팅 챔피언
with your Dorothy Hamill poster
and you were all--
로리는 태어날 때 꼬리가 있었어 / 뭐?
Laurie was born with a tail! / What?
그래! 로리는 태어날 때 꼬리가 있었어!
Yeah! Laurie was born with a tail!
너 미워!
I hate you!
사실이야
That's true.
여보, 그 목걸이 전당포에 맡겨서
정말 미안해요
Okay, Red. I'm very sorry
I pawned that necklace.
괜찮아, 생각해 봤는데
별거 아니더라고
That's okay. I've been thinking
about it, and it's no big deal.
지난 일은 다 지난 일이지 뭐
Let's just let bygones be bygones.
그렇지 않아?
What do you say, pretty lady?
뭔 짓을 한 거예요?
What'd you do?
몇달전에 당신 아버지가 주신
주머니시계를 전당포에 맡겼어
A few months ago, I pawned the
pocketwatch your dad gave me.
우린 비긴 거니까
다 털어버리자고
So, we're even, let's just
get on with our lives.
여보, 어떻게 그럴 수가 있어요?
Oh Red, how could you?
Well, Kitty, who the hell needs
a damn pocketwatch?
그딴 주머니시계를 누가 써?
"지금 몇시죠?"
"글쎄요, 주머니 속을 보고 알려드리죠"
What time is it? I don't
know, I'll check my pocket.
이게 뭐야! 바보같잖아
See, I mean, that's just stupid.
여보
Oh, Red.
잔디깎이랑 에릭꺼 오래된 축음기도
전당포에 맡겼어
And I pawned the lawn mower,
and Eric's old phonograph player,
제설기도
and the snowblower.
우리한테 제설기가 있었어요?
We had a snowblower?
사실 밥네 꺼였어
Actually, it was Bob's.
근데, 왜 저한테 그렇게 화를 냈어요?
Well, why did you get so mad at me?
나 자신에게 화가 났던거야
I got mad at myself.
가족을 부양하는 건 남자 일이야
근데 그럴 능력이 없어서
Look, it's the man's job to support
the family, and if he can't do that,
물건을 전당포에 맡기는 것도
남자 몫이란 말이야
it's the man's job to pawn the things
to feed the family that he can't support.
알았어요
Okay. Okay.
You know, Bob's been
looking for that snowblower.
밥이 제설기를 계속 찾더라구요
나도 알아
Yeah, I know, Kitty.
나만 믿어
내가 핑계거리를 쥐어 짜내고 있어
And believe you me,
I'm running out of stories.
그러니까, 니말은
내가 악마랑 같이 잤다는 거야?
So what you're saying is,
I slept with the devil?
바로 그거지
Exactly.
나한테는 점이라고 했단 말야
She told me it was a birthmark.
점은 점이지. 태어날 때 꼬리를
자르면서 생겨난 점 말야
It is a birthmark. From where
they cut off her tail at birth.
얘들아, 나 사실 이번 일이
약간 신경쓰이고 있어
Guys, I'm actually starting to
feel a little bad about this.
맞아, 다른 사람의 비밀을
폭로하는 건 옳지 않아
Yeah, it is not right to reveal
other peoples' secrets.
난 이 문제에 대해서는
오줌싸개의 의견에 동의해
I'm going to have to agree with
Doctor Pee Pee on this one.
안녕, 얘들아
잘 지내니, 마이클?
Hello, boys. And how are you, Michael?
별로야. 아주 역겨운
사실을 알게 됐거든
Well, not so good. I just got
some very disturbing news.
니가 계속 비참하길 바랄께
Well, I hope you're very unhappy.
페즈, 얘기 좀 할까? / 그래
Fez, can I talk to you? / Yes.
페즈, 어제밤 너무 고마웠어
Fez, I just want to thank you for last night.
내가 어제밤에 평소처럼 깜찍하지
못했던 거 나도 알아, 미안해
I know I wasn't my super-cute
self, and I'm sorry.
그렇지만 넌 정말 좋은 친구야
But you're a really good friend.
그래도, 친구 이상의 것을
기대해도 될까?
But Jackie, I was hoping that perhaps
we could be more than friends?
글쎄, 꿈꾸는 거야 자유니까
Well, hope springs eternal, Fez.
그냥 멀리서 날 흠모하면서
계속 기다리는게 어떻겠니?
How about you just keep worshipping
me from afar, and stay available.
혹시 모르잖아
Just in case.
날 위해서 그래 줄래?
You would do that for me?
그거 정말 달콤한 제안이구나
That's a sweet deal.
약속의 의미로 키스해줄래?
Should we kiss on it?
그럼
Sure.
안녕
Bye.
못 참아
넌 인제 죽었어
Alright, that's it.
You're a dead man.
아~뵤~!
Hiyaaa!
좋은 꿈 꿔라, 오줌싸개야
Sweet dreams, Doctor Pee Pee.
오 예!
Oh yeah.
번역수정 : 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24